Hello friends welcome forever video in today's
video we will talk about ICC Life
Insurance Company Limited, the
company's quarter one result has been released,
what kind of result is going to be there, so we are going to
discuss that in today's
video, if you are new to the channel then subscribe
and like the video because it takes a
lot of hard work to make such videos, so
let's start, so
today there is a decline of about 1.5%
in the company and the company's main work here is
related to insurance like life
insurance, health insurance, many types of
insurance companies provide here, if we
talk about its market cap, then the
market cap is approximately 80000 590 crores
and the current price is seen here
trending around 500 74
and a low of 381 has been set, the divide in 52 weeks is
very low, it is seen around 0 point 10 percent, the
face value is
seen,
whereas according to the score of Pitrosh, it
is average for the long term, whereas the Gram
number  If we look at it from the perspective of this, it is quite
expensive,
around 1168 crores. Let us also see the quarterly results,
what kind of results are being seen
in this quarter,
in the last quarter, in March,
where the sales in water were of 10084 crores, it has
increased to
around 23384 crores and if you see, a huge
jump has been seen, it has almost
doubled, its
sales have expanded in one quarter, that is, if we
talk about expenses, then the expenses have also been very high, the
operating profit of the company was seen in mines here,
in the last quarter, where there was 416
crores in mines, that of Ghat has become 280
crores, if we
talk about net profit, then the net profit
here was seen to decrease from 200 35 crores to around 206 crores, if we talk about
Epic, then it
decreased from one rupee 64 paise to ₹143,
whereas this time, we had talked about tax here,
despite that, there has been a
loss in profit here, the net
profit here is seen to be in loss only.
Compared to the previous quarter,
investors should see what kind
of action they got. If
we talk about motor, then the
promoters' holding remains the same here,
its holding has increased, whereas if we
talk about public, then the public's holding has
decreased and see, the promoted
investors have seen positive
investor action here. Thanks but watching, see you in the
next video.